Francis Gevrier Guittard papers, Inclusive: 1811-1960, undated, Bulk: 1900-1940
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Literary Productions, 1811-1960, undated; 4
  - Notebook: History 203 (4 of 6), undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Notebook: History 203 (5 of 6), undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Notebook: History 203 (6 of 6), undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Notebook: History 205 (1 of 11), undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Notebook: History 205 (2 of 11), undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Notebook: History 205 (3 of 11), undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Notebook: History 205 (4 of 11), undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Notebook: History 205 (5 of 11), undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Notebook: History 205 (6 of 11), undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Notebook: History 205 (7 of 11), undated (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Notebook: History 205 (8 of 11), undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Notebook: History 205 (9 of 11), undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Notebook: History 205 (10 of 11), undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Notebook: History 205 (11 of 11), undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Notebook: History 206 (1 of 10), undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Notebook: History 206 (2 of 10), undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Notebook: History 206 (3 of 10), undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Notebook: History 206 (4 of 10), undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Notebook: History 206 (5 of 10), undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Notebook: History 206 (6 of 10), undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Notebook: History 206 (7 of 10), undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Notebook: History 206 (8 of 10), undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Notebook: History 206 (9 of 10), undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Notebook: History 206 (10 of 10), undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Notebook: History 208, undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Notebook: History 209 (1 of 7), undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Notebook: History 209 (2 of 7), undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Notebook: History 209 (3 of 7), undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Notebook: History 209 (4 of 7), undated (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Notebook: History 209 (5 of 7), undated (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Notebook: History 209 (6 of 7), undated (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Notebook: History 209 (7 of 7), undated (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Notebook: History 210 (1 of 12), undated (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Notebook: History 210 (2 of 12), undated (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Notebook: History 210 (3 of 12), undated (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Notebook: History 210 (4 of 12), undated (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Notebook: History 210 (5 of 12), undated (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Notebook: History 210 (6 of 12), undated (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Notebook: History 210 (7 of 12), undated (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Notebook: History 210 (8 of 12), undated (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Notebook: History 210 (9 of 12), undated (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Notebook: History 210 (10 of 12), undated (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Notebook: History 210 (11 of 12), undated (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Notebook: History 210 (12 of 12), undated (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Notebook: History 217 (1 of 3), undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Notebook: History 217 (2 of 3), undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Notebook: History 217 (3 of 3), undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Notebook: History 218 (1 of 3), undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Notebook: History 218 (2 of 3), undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Notebook: History 218 (3 of 3), undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Notebook: History 219 (1 of 4), undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Notebook: History 219 (2 of 4), undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Notebook: History 219 (3 of 4), undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Notebook: History 219 (4 of 4), undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Notebook: History 222 (1 of 12), undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Notebook: History 222 (2 of 12), undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Notebook: History 222 (3 of 12), undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Notebook: History 222 (4 of 12), undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Notebook: History 222 (5 of 12), undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Notebook: History 222 (6 of 12), undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Notebook: History 222 (7 of 12), undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Notebook: History 222 (8 of 12), undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Notebook: History 222 (9 of 12), undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Notebook: History 222 (10 of 12), undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Notebook: History 222 (11 of 12), undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Notebook: History 222 (12 of 12), undated (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Notebook: History 224 (1 of 9), undated (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Notebook: History 224 (2 of 9), undated (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Notebook: History 224 (3 of 9), undated (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Notebook: History 224 (4 of 9), undated (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Notebook: History 224 (5 of 9), undated (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Notebook: History 224 (6 of 9), undated (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Notebook: History 224 (7 of 9), undated (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Notebook: History 224 (8 of 9), undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Notebook: History 224 (9 of 9), undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Notebook: History 226 (1 of 7), undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Notebook: History 226 (2 of 7), undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Notebook: History 226 (3 of 7), undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Notebook: History 226 (4 of 7), undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Notebook: History 226 (5 of 7), undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Notebook: History 226 (6 of 7), undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Notebook: History 226 (7 of 7), undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Notebook: History 227 (1 of 6), undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Notebook: History 227 (2 of 6), undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Notebook: History 227 (3 of 6), undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Notebook: History 227 (4 of 6), undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Notebook: History 227 (5 of 6), undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Notebook: History 227 (6 of 6), undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Notebook: Medical, undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Notebook: Untitled, undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Notebook: “My Funny Book”: Francis Gevrier Guittard, undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Notebook: Student Work: Thesis Topics, 1921-1947 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Notebook: Thesis Topics, undated (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Notes: Baylor University: History Department, 1926, undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Notes: Jokes, undated (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Obituaries: Francis Gevrier Guittard, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Outlines: General (1 of 3), 1901, undated (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Outlines: General (2 of 3), 1901, undated (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Outlines: General (3 of 3), 1901, undated (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Pamphlet: Pi Gamma Mu, 1934-1935 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Periodical: Baylor University Bulletin: Texas Peace Congress Proceedings, 1907-1908 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Periodical: Literary: Baylor University Literary Societies, 1894 April (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Periodical: Motherhood Magazine: Texas Congress of Mothers and Parent-Teacher Association, 1922 November 21-23 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Periodical: Texas Bar Journal: Clarence Guittard, 1941 June (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Periodical: The Baylor Line: “Death Claims Dr. Francis G. Guittard”, 1950 May-June (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Periodical: The Baylor Monthly, 1927 April-May (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Periodical: The Baylor Monthly, 1927 August- 1928 August (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Periodical: The Baylor Monthly, 1928 December -1931 June (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Periodical: The Literary Digest, 1922 January 21 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Periodical: The Literary Digest, 1927 March 12 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Poem: “The Lady of the Lake”: Sir Walter Scott, undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Political Materials: General, undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Postcard Album: Cleveland, Ohio, undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Postcard Album: Louisville and Nashville Railroad, undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Postcard Album: “Rijksmuseum Amsterdam”, undated (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Postcard Album: Potsdam, Germany, undated (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Postcard Album: “San Antonio Album”: Paul Wagner, undated (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Postcard Album: “Souvenir of Milwaukee”, undated (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Postcard Album: “The University of Chicago”, 1898 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Postcards: Europe: General, undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Postcards: Florence, Italy, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Postcards: London, England (1 of 3), undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Postcards: London, England (2 of 3), undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Postcards: London, England (3 of 3), undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Postcards: Maryland (1 of 2), undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Postcards: Maryland (2 of 2), undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Postcards: Massachusetts: Revolutionary War Sites, undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Postcards: Milan, Italy, undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Postcards: New York City, 1920, undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Postcards: Pennsylvania (1 of 4), undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Postcards: Pennsylvania (2 of 4), undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Postcards: Pennsylvania (3 of 4), undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Postcards: Pennsylvania (4 of 4), undated (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Postcards: Rome, Italy (1 of 3), undated (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Postcards: Rome, Italy (2 of 3), undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Postcards: Rome, Italy (3 of 3), undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Postcards: Switzerland (1 of 3), undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Postcards: Switzerland (2 of 3), undated (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Postcards: Switzerland (3 of 3), undated (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Postcards: United States: General, undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Postcards: Virginia, undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Postcards: Washington, D.C. (1 of 3), undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Postcards: Washington, D.C. (2 of 3), undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Postcards: Washington, D.C. (3 of 3), undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Printed Materials: General, 1897-1935, undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Printed Materials: Baylor University: Baylor Round Table, 1930, undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Printed Materials: Baylor University: History Department, 1934-1950, undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Printed Materials: Chinese, undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Program: “30 Masterpieces”: Dallas Museum of Fine Arts, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Program: Baylor University Commencement, 1950 May 28 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Program: Baylor University: Founder’s Day, 1945 February 1 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Program: Baylor University: Honorary Degree: Harry Truman, 1947 March 6 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Program: Democratic National Convention: Houston, Texas, 1928 June 26-29 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Program: Gone with the Wind, circa 1940 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Program: Holmes County Centennial and Street Fair: Millersburg, Ohio, 1925 October (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Program: “Outline Study of King John”: Kate Friend, undated (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Program: Texas Cotton Palace Exposition, 1929 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Program: Une Vraie Follie: Paris, France, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Program: University of Chicago: Forty-Second Convocation, 1902 June 17 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Program: Waco Shakespeare Club, undated (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Programs: General, 1892-1937, undated (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Programs: Baylor University, 1894-1946 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Programs: Commencement: High Schools, 1939-1944 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Programs: Plays, 1896-1947 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Programs: Teachers, 1893-1897, undated (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Programs: Universities, 1898-1940 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Programs: Waco Literary Club, 1922-1926 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Programs: Waco Literary Club, 1931-1933 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Report: “Tracing a Bill from Its Introduction Until It Becomes a Law”, 1901 July 10 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Roll: Reunion of Former Students: Magnolia, Arkansas, 1930 June (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Screenplay: “From Punkin Ridge”: H. Elliott McBride, 1873 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Speech: Erisophian Literary Society: Baylor University, 1905 September 16 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Speech: Magnolia High School: “Making and Investing a Life”, 1930 May 23 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Thesis: “The Life of Francis Gevrier Guittard”: Louise Moore Cagle, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Yearbook: Baylor Round Table, 1922-1923, 1932-1933 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Yearbook: Baylor Round Table, 1935-1936, 1940-1941 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Yearbook: Baylor Round Table, 1941-1942 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Yearbook: Woman’s Auxiliary: First Baptist Church of Waco, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Notes: Dissertation: Concerning Theodore Roosevelt (1 of 2), undated (Box 24 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Notes: Dissertation: Concerning Theodore Roosevelt (2 of 2), undated (Box 24 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Notes: Baptists: W.L. Phelps, undated (Box 25 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Notes: Baylor University: Marshals, circa 1949 (Box 25 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Notes: Dissertation: Bibliographic Sources (1 of 2), undated (Box 25 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Notes: Dissertation: Bibliographic Sources (2 of 2), undated (Box 25 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Notes: England, undated (Box 25 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - Notes: Presidents of the United States, undated (Box 25 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - Notes: William Allen White, undated (Box 25 OVZ, Folder 7)
  - Notes: William Morris, undated (Box 25 OVZ, Folder 8)
  - Political Materials: Poster: Alfred Smith and Joe Robinson, 1928 (Box [1068] OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Printed Materials: Chinese, undated (Box [1068] OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Political Materials: Canvas: Calvin Coolidge, undated (Box 38 OVZ, Folder 1)
- Genealogical Materials, 1912-1937, undated; 5
  The following series contains genealogical notes and books concerning the Gevrier, Guittard, and Tombaugh families. The materials are in good condition.
  - Book: Tombaugh History, 1728-1930: Reno Tombaugh (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Notebook: French: Guittard Family, undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Notes: Gevrier Family, undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Notes: Guittard Family, undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Notes: Tombaugh Family, 1912 March 21 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Notes: Tombaugh Family, 1928-1937, undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Photographic Materials, 1893-1952, undated; 6
  This series consists of ninety-six magic lantern slides of scenes throughout Europe during World War I as well as photographs of members of the Guittard family, many unidentified persons, and a few locations. They are arranged by individual and place name and then alphabetized. While most of the photographic materials are undated, they appear to be from the late nineteenth and early twentieth centuries. The items in this series are in good condition.
  Index Terms
  Genres
  Daguerreotype; Lantern slide; Photograph album; Portrait photograph
  - General, 1893, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - General (1 of 9), undated (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - General (2 of 9), undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - General (3 of 9), undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - General (4 of 9), undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - General (5 of 9), undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - General (6 of 9), undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - General (7 of 9), undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - General (8 of 9), undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - General (9 of 9), undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Alaska, 1948 May (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Alwin Meias Guittard (1 of 2), undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Alwin Meias Guittard (2 of 2), undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Arthur J. Guittard, 1908 November-1924, undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Baylor University History Department (1 of 6), 1915, undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Baylor University History Department (2 of 6), 1915, undated (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Baylor University History Department (3 of 6), 1915, undated (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Baylor University History Department (4 of 6), 1915, undated (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Baylor University History Department (5 of 6), 1915, undated (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Baylor University History Department (6 of 6), 1915, undated (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Claude Guittard, undated (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Ewing Family, undated (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Francis Gevrier Guittard (1 of 2), undated (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Francis Gevrier Guittard (2 of 2), undated (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Printing Plate: Francis Gevrier Guittard, undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Japan, undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Magic Lantern Slides Descriptions, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - New Bedford, Ohio (1 of 2), undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - New Bedford, Ohio (2 of 2), undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Rosine Duprey, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Victor Guittard, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Virgil Guittard, 1906 November 11, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Virgil Guittard, undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 1: WWI: Austrian Building OperationsDLWomen Mixing Mortar. (1 of 17), undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 1: WWI: In the Harvest Fields in GermanyDLWomen and Children taking the Places of the Men at the Front. (2 of 17), undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 1: WWI: In FlandersDLBelgian Officers and Corporals Studying Maps and Giving Instructions to Subordinates. (European War.) (3 of 17), undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 1: WWI: With the Belgian Army at the Front: Inspection of Rifles. (European War.) (4 of 17), undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 1: WWI: The Fortress and Bridge, Dinant, Belgium. (5 of 17), undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 1: WWI: Model of Warship of the 18th Century, Musee of Antiquities, Ghent, Belgium. (6 of 17), undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 1: WWI: Ruins of a Sugar Mill Bombarded by the Germans. (European War.) (7 of 17), undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 1: WWI: Trenches of the Allies Among the Dunes in the Middle of Brambles On the Coast of Flanders. (European War.) (8 of 17), undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 1: WWI: Troop of French Cyclist Scouts in the Enemy’s Country. (European War.) (9 of 17), undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 1: WWI: French Infantry Excavating for Trenches. (European War.) (10 of 17), undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 1: WWI: A Hussar Firing Through a Loophole, in the French Trenches. (European War.) (11 of 17), undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 1: WWI: Shelters With Gardens Behind. In the French Trenches. (European War.) (12 of 17), undated (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 1: WWI: A Peaceful Scene in the TrenchesDLAt the Front. (European War.) (13 of 17), undated (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 1: WWI: Belgian Troops Advancing to Make a Bayonet Charge On the Coast of Flanders. (European War.) (14 of 17), undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 1: WWI: French Soldiers in Camp near Round House, Tsien-Tsien, China. (15 of 17), undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 1: WWI: French Infantry (16 of 17), undated (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 1: WWI: French Battleship “Leon Gambetta.” Quebec Tercentenary, July 1908. (17 of 17), undated (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 2: WWI: One of the Famous French 75 Cannons Elevated Firing at an Aeroplane. (European War.) (1 of 16), undated (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 2: WWI: A Part of the Great Army with Which Russia Hoped to Drive the Japanese from the Asiatic Mainland, Port Arthur, Manchuria. (2 of 16), undated (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 2: WWI: Russian Uhlans Riding Through the Main Street, “The Tachsen Place,” Warsaw, Russia. (European War.) (3 of 16), undated (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 2: WWI: Russia Fleet in Port Arthur Harbor. (4 of 16), undated (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 2: WWI: The King Edward Horse Guards, London, England. (European War.) (5 of 16), undated (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 2: WWI: English Army HorsesDLEncampment at Alexander Palaces, London, England. (6 of 16), undated (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 2: WWI: Supply Wagons Ready to Leave for the Aid of Troops at the Front. (European War.) (7 of 16), undated (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 2: WWI: A Part of England’s Cosmopolitan Army. (8 of 16), undated (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 2: WWI: The 48th Highlanders of Toronto. (9 of 16), undated (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 2: WWI: In the French Trenches, Showing a Cross Erected Over the Graves of Dead Heroes. (European War.) (10 of 16), undated (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 2: WWI: Ruins of a Mansion in the Pathway of the German Guns, Senlis, France. (European War.) (11 of 16), undated (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 2: WWI: Artillery ManeuversDLThe Decisive Favor of the Present War. (12 of 16), undated (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 2: WWI: Battery of Artillery. (13 of 16), undated (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 2: WWI: French Guns, Paris, France. (14 of 16), undated (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 2: WWI: Death Dealing Devices of Ancient and Modern Times Captured by the Allied Forces. (15 of 16), undated (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 2: WWI: The “Indomitable”DLThe English Battleship Who Sunk the German “Bluecher” on Sunday, January 24, 1916. (16 of 16), undated (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 3: WWI: Under Arrest Near the Danube River. (1 of 16), undated (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 3: WWI: Band of Cuirassier Guards Marching to Parade Ground, Berlin, Germany. (2 of 16), undated (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 3: WWI: A Group of German Officers. (3 of 16), undated (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 3: WWI: Guarding the Entrance to a Stronghold at Long[EL] a Fortified French Town on the Belgian Frontier Held by German Forces. (European War.) (4 of 16), undated (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 3: WWI: Wooden Bridge Built Over River Meuse by Germans to Replace One Allies Destroyed in their Retreat from Belgium. (5 of 16), undated (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 3: WWI: Mounted Gun and German Gunners at Montmedy, a Town of the French Frontier, at Present Under Teutonic Power (European War). (6 of 16), undated (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 3: WWI: A Modern Type of SubmarineDLA Twentieth Century Product. (7 of 16), undated (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 3: WWI: A Bird of PreyDLZeppelin Flying Over a German Town. (European War.) (8 of 16), undated (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 3: WWI: Officers entering the Cradle of a Captive Balloon. (9 of 16), undated (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 3: WWI: German Machine Gun Division in Action. (European War.) (10 of 16), undated (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 3: WWI: A Barber with the German Army Serving His Patrons in the Open. (11 of 16), undated (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 3: WWI: German PeasantsDLA Peaceful Scene in the Inter[EL] Away From the Strife of War. (12 of 16), undated (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 3: WWI: [Map of the Eastern Front] (13 of 16), undated (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 3: WWI: German Soldiers on the Eastern Front Enjoying a Brief Respite in the Forest While Awaiting Rations. (14 of 16), undated (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 3: WWI: Military Review, Emperor’s Birthday, Nov. 3, 1904, Tokio, Japan. (15 of 16), undated (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 3: WWI: Barb Wire Entanglements Cut by the German Soldiers to Hasten their Attack on Russian Lines. (16 of 16), undated (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Magic Lantern Slides: Box 4: WWI: Tartar Merchants at the Fair, Nizhini Novgorod, Russia. (1 of 14), undated (Box 19, Folder 50)